[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Go! Leave!
You're useless anyway!
You're really leaving
your family for your mistress?
Are you stupid?
[SONYA SOBS]
Do you know I can
get you jailed?
Sonya...
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
we both know
we're not happy together.
I'm sorry but I can't live
with you anymore!
[SONYA]
Why all of a sudden, Erman?
All along I thought we're okay.
But you weren't happy anymore.
You should've
at least told me about it,
so we could've fixed it
together.
Not like this.
You're blindsiding me
with your decision.
There's no fixing this.
I have been understanding
and been supportive of you
and your career
as a dermatologist,
but this lavish lifestyle
and your social status
aren't for me!
You keep wanting for more
and I just wanted you
and our family!
Don't make it my fault
that I earn more than you!
I don't care
if you earn more than me
because I earn just fine!
[ERMAN BREATHING SHAKILY]
[VOICE BREAKING]
But you were never proud of me.
[ERMAN EXHALES HEAVILY]
If you leave now,
there will be no coming back.
[MARLA SOBS]
[ERMAN] I won't be coming back.
[SOBBING]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Marla...
dear...
[SOBBING]
[ERMAN] Marla...
Marla...
I'm sorry.
Do you want to come with me?
I mean...
is this the life you want?
You can come with me.
Come on.
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
One day,
you'll understand me.
I love you, Marla.
I'll come back for you.
I promise.
[SOBBING]
[SMOOCHES]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[MARLA SOBBING]
[SIGHS HEAVILY]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR OPENS]
- [DOOR CLOSES]
- [MARLA SNIFFLES]
Marla?
Marla...
What happened?
Are you okay?
[SOBBING]
Dad left us.
I'm sorry.
He was asking me
to come with him, but...
I chose to stay.
Is that what you want?
I don't know.
I'm so confused, Cole...
[SOBBING]
[COLE] Marla...
Marla, I'll...
I'll always be here, okay?
I would never leave you.
I promise.
[MARLA SOBBING]
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SOBBING]
I love you, Cole.
It'll be okay.
Don't worry,
I'll always be here.
I will always be here, okay?
[MARLA]
The laws of thermodynamics
are the foundational
principles of physics
that define how energy,
heat, and work
interact within a system
and its surroundings.
[MCKENNA] Your daughters
are suspended for five days.
[COLE] Was it so hard
to have one mistake
so I can be Top 1
even for just one quarter...
just one quarter,
so Dad won't be mad at me?!
Do you still love me?
Do you know
the Collatz Conjecture?
Even if I wait
for half a century...
that's how much I love you.
[MARLA]
The laws of thermodynamics
offer a powerful metaphor
for destruction.
It shows a transformation
towards disorder,
leading up
to an eventual breakdown.
The question is...
am I ready for the destruction
I'm about to bring?
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
Marla?
Marla.
Hm?
- Girly pops.
- You okay?
Yeah.
Are you ready?
- Yeah.
- Yes.
Go.
Shit. The firewalls...
[SCOFFS]
Damn you, Migo!
What does Migo
have to do with this?
It's just a hunch.
A hunch?
Please expound.
I'm having a hard time
hacking Cole's profiles.
I know Migo.
He's probably protecting
my brother
which I find puzzling.
Why would Migo do that?
Damage control.
Maybe they're hiding
something online
so they need someone like Migo.
But why won't your brother
just ask you for help?
Mm-hmm.
We're not actually
the best of friends.
[APRIL] Not anymore.
[ISOBEL] What a desperate move.
Aren't you better
than your boyfriend
when it comes to these things?
I'm not better.
I'm the best.
And correction, he's my ex.
Whoa, in fairness.
You're single, too, girl?
[GIGGLES]
Welcome to the club!
Hm?
You're the only one
with a boyfriend.
What? When will you leave him?
Don't tell me
you're single as well?
My gosh.
[SIGHS SHARPLY]
I don't know.
You don't? You flirt.
[ISOBEL] Let's phish a member.
Send a fake security alert.
Who's the dumbest guy
in the group?
Lester?
- Ant?
- Huh?
No.
Ugh, they're all dumb!
[NYX GASPS]
All these happenings are getting
more intense, you know?
My scalp's so sweating.
Oh, my gosh.
"But wait, wait, wait,"
says Waitey the Pooh.
Hmm...
I think I remember something.
Something Ant mentioned.
Who's my ex, by the way.
Hmm...
He and his friends
have this group chat.
You can pretend
to be IT support, you know.
So you can infiltrate the GC.
Infiltrate? The GC...
No, no, no. That's right!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
I read about this one time.
To quote the author,
we can do session hijacking.
So we use the web-based
version of the chat
and digitally "clone" the
session by scanning the QR code
and stealing
the browser's session cookies.
Or we can also
manipulate the server
by adding another member
without notifying
the other members.
Like ghost admin
vulnerabilities.
Yeah.
What do you think?
Yeah, I was about
to say that too.
- You just beat me to it.
- Really?
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
I'll trick a target
into downloading
a Remote Access Trojan.
It's disguised
as a harmless file.
Once we're in,
we can see their screen
and read chat histories
in real-time.
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
We're in!
[NYX] My gosh!
Girls, I think I cannot...
This is too much, like...
[INHALES SHARPLY]
I cannot look, you know.
Just open your eyes, Nyx!
[COLE] Ant! Bro! Are you sure?
Nyx is a 0! You're a 10!
You could do
so much better, bro!
[ANT] Thanks, bro!
But you're the 10, bro.
You're so handsome, you know?
[LESTER] Dude, she looks gay
just like her parents.
Gay?
- What's with Nyx?
- Did he say gay?
She any good?
Oh, yeah.
So good.
[ANT] Uh... She's nice.
Nice?
[COLE] Can I borrow her, bro?
Share your blessings!
[LESTER] You can only look, bro.
That's my baby girl.
[COLE] Dude, my bad.
Daphne's really so hot.
[ANT] Dude! Don't you
have a dick pic?
I wanna know
if Daphne can hold it together
if you know what I mean.
[COMPUTER CHIMING]
This asshole!
[SNIFFLES]
[GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
[LESTER] Idol!
You the man, Cole! Damn!
Isobel is so hot!
I bet she can handle me
and you together, bruh!
[ANT] Let me join!
[COMPUTER CHIMING]
[LESTER] I'm getting horny AF!
You're one lucky dude!
When are you going to get laid?
Or Isobel's enough for you?
[COLE] Patience, bro.
It won't be long
and Marla's gonna give in.
Isobel is just my appetizer.
But Marla, has always
been my main course!
[LESTER] You're the man, bro!
[ANT] Who's dessert?
Oh, no.
What's happening?
The messages are disappearing.
- Do something!
- What's happening?
- [ISOBEL] Fix it!
- [APRIL] I am!
Oh, no!
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
- Sh--
- I lost all access.
[WHINES]
- Damn it!
- Shit.
[HUFFING]
So, they're just
comparing dicks?
Girl? You okay, girl?
Girl?
Marla.
Who's that?
The way Lester speaks
in that GC...
is not the Lester I know.
So disgusting.
Was he even the guy I loved?
[ISOBEL] Wow.
The one who says he "loves me?"
[ISOBEL] Help yourself. Stop!
Boys will be boys.
They're all trash!
Screw them!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
We're gonna make them pay.
[SNIFFLES]
Each and every one of them.
Okay, fine!
Nothing will leak
if we didn't send nude photos.
Alright, it's our fault.
We were dumb, we were stupid,
we were vulnerable,
we sent those pictures.
But if we're going down,
we take everyone with us!
Finally,
something I can agree on.
We'll destroy them.
Make them suffer
until they beg us to stop!
And if we can't rely
on the rules,
then fuck it,
we'll make our own rules!
[SNIFFLES, EXHALES DEEPLY]
Revenge will be ours.
Revenge.
Huh?
We will take our revenge!
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
Goosebumps.
Revenge. Huh.
So...
if we do this revenge thingy,
how are we going to do it?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
I have an idea.
We...
we will study!
Oh.
What?
We will... we will study.
We will study hard.
We have to maintain
a high average.
We need to outrank the boys.
And then the school will have
no choice but to reinstate us.
- Hmm...
Remember,
I suggested that before?
Yellow dress, remember?
Study hard?
That's your big idea?
After your big speech earlier.
You even cussed them, yeah?
What do you mean, study hard?
Are you a nerd?
Come on, are you serious, Marla?
Is this a study group?
I was already hyped up.
Sorry, top of my head.
Why don't you give
suggestions then?
But you know, girls...
I think Marla has a point.
Like, revenge?
With our tiny selves?
Revenge is a big word!
Then revenge becomes
an empty word.
Empty words, quote, empty words!
It's so trivial!
Trivial?!
It's just, you know...
we're going against the boys?
Oh, my gosh, I think
that idea feels
kinda scary to me.
I'm so scared.
[SIGHS]
[DAPHNE] Hmm...
Well, Lester is a bit
of a wild card.
He's crazy
and will just punch whoever.
I don't even know
why I love him.
[SCOFFS] 'Cause he has money?
- Obviously.
- Hey, Dora.
You're saying I'm a gold digger?
No.
You love Lester.
Even if he's a monster,
you still wanna
force yourself into him.
And you thought he loved you.
[SCOFFS]
But did he visit you
at your home?
Where's your home, again?
- Cubao.
- Cubao!
Did he even personally
check in with you?
No. Right?
And now you're scared.
You're overthinking
all of the probabilities
because there's no possibility
that he will ever love you,
Dessalyn!
And now,
you're afraid
for your future.
Nyx...
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
...you're still
head over heels with Ant.
But he was just using you.
Didn't you see
all of those messages
in the group chat?
You were just zero?
He made you look stupid
just to make the boys laugh.
You're just a joke to him.
He doesn't give a shit
about you.
April!
I'll destroy Migo.
Marla...
I know I'm the last person
that you would trust,
but if you would seek
and dedicate yourself
to this plan,
I will follow you
to the depths of fire,
any element there is,
so that you,
and all of us can succeed.
And, I know you love Cole.
But I'm sorry...
he doesn't love you!
He doesn't love you!
He doesn't love me.
He doesn't love anyone
but himself.
I know
that you have a different idea
of what revenge is,
but don't ignore
what it truly is.
So by doing this, maybe,
just maybe...
you'd realize
that you deserve better.
That we all do.
Okay.
Okay?
Let's do this.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Hide! Hide!
- Hey, over here.
- Hide, hide, hide!
- Don't move. Quiet.
- [KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[ADOLF] April!
[BANGING ON DOOR]
Who told you that you
could lock your room, huh?
I didn't mean to.
What bullshit is this?
Huh?
Nude photos?
Have you no shame? Huh?
Is that how a woman behaves?!
To think you're the child
of the Commanding Officer
of a military base.
You bring shame to my rank!
Was that your intention? Huh?
What would people say?
You wanna ruin my good name?
No.
What?
What did you say?
No, sir.
I didn't send you
to Omni-Standard
so that you can be a whore!
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Just be thankful that I
am a member
of the school board.
Pull yourself together.
Or do you want to end up
like your mother?
Huh?!
It won't happen again, sir.
April--
Maybe later.
- Get inside.
- Sir...
Why did you let this
happen to your sister?
It wasn't my fault, sir.
- [SLAPS]
- [COLE GRUNTS]
[ADOLF] The gall to talk back!
Your sister's photos got leaked,
along with your girlfriend's!
And you did nothing!
What kind of man are you?!
Do you think I didn't know
that your ranking dropped?
Top 5?
Top 5.
I don't have a son who's Top 5!
Top 5 is for idiots!
I'm Top 1, sir.
How'd that happen?
The girls were all suspended...
that's why I'm Top 1, sir.
- [SMACKS]
- [COLE GASPS]
[COLE] Sir...
You think I'd be pleased
that you got back to Top 1
because your girlfriend's
nude photos were leaked?
Is that it?
- Marla and I are over, sir.
- Good!
You'll do everything
to wipe out this scandal.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
- [SLAPS]
- Yes, sir. [WHIMPERS]
[CRYING] Yes, sir. Yes, sir...
- [MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [COLE CRYING]
- [SLAMS DOOR]
- Aah!
Aah!
You know,
this is all your fault.
Dragging me into your stupidity.
I wasn't the one
who leaked my photos!
Are you talking back?
Just lie low until the scandal
goes away, okay?
Whatever.
"Whatever"?
Cole!
What? Huh?
Don't let it get to your head.
Don't be complacent, missy.
You're just a mistress's child.
Don't ever forget that.
Know your place.
[SOFT RUSTLING]
Is someone here?
No. Get out.
Who's there?
- Get out, Cole!
- Who's there?
Get out of my room!
[MOROSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR SLAMS]
[HUFFS]
Don't come out yet.
Please.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
[CRYING SOFTLY]
[SNIFFLING, CRYING]
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[MARLA] Welcome to our
very first meeting!
I'm so excited
for our little revenge group!
And thank you so much
to Isobel
for being so nice
and for opening her home to us.
[ISOBEL] Sure. Anytime.
Okay!
Let's get down to business.
Speaking of let's get down
to business...
move.
I'll handle this.
- Huh? Why?
- Just sit down, come on.
I've prepared a presentation.
- Maybe later.
- No, I have a presentation.
- Later.
- Sis, I didn't wear this choker
just so I won't present.
Want me to choke you
with this? Sit down.
- Okay.
- Good.
Now we're getting somewhere.
And let's go.
Because I'm such a girl scout,
I've prepared a Canva!
You dig that? [CHUCKLES]
I dig that! Okay, game!
Since we've got
all this planning to do,
it is imperative--
Imperative?!
It is imperative
that we get to know
each other's superpowers
and strengths
so that we know
how to work with each other
and what adjustments to make.
What do you mean by superpowers?
Because you're the first
to ask about superpowers,
let me start with you.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
[THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[NYX] Damn!
Girl, you look so hot.
You're welcome.
Because we're talking
superpowers,
your superpowers
are all about tech.
You're the Queen of Tech!
Your tech, her tech, my tech...
that's everyone's tech tech!
Yes, gonna te-te-tech that!
Okay, next, next, next.
[THRILLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
As we all know,
Isobel's forte is witchcraft.
Demon Slayer...
or maybe the Princess from Hell?
- Agree!
- Remember, you're in my house.
Just kidding.
She agreed, though.
I just got carried away, sorry.
Moving on,
let me hype you, girl.
That's what I'm building at.
We all know you're
the Queen of Chemical Compounds.
Ah, you're like
the potion extraordinaire.
Wow! You're the hot topic there.
And next,
but not the least.
[THRILLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[NYX] Damn, is that pink?
You know I hate pink.
But is that really pink?
Well, it is pink!
So of course, Marla,
you're like Jean Grey.
Wow! X-Men!
Or maybe, Professor X!
Photographic memory.
Well, well, well, well, well,
says William Herschel,
"What a gift, indeed."
[CHUCKLES]
Really something.
Really very useful
in all intents and purposes...
You remember all the things,
but I remember the boys!
Kidding! Just kidding!
So I can see you doubting
and you're thinking...
what can I offer?
You're thinking
she's got nothing. Psh!
Beauty!
Oh, more than that, girl!
Behold!
I look so gorgeous there.
[GIGGLES]
So, if you think I got nothing,
you're dead wrong.
- Inventions.
- [NYX] Mm-hmm.
I've seen you whip up something
from scratch.
You're actually
the most talented here...
Oh, don't.
Well, second to me.
Always have to be on top,
but, yes, as the Queen...
I mean, the president
of the Robotics Club,
I can do anything,
even from scratch,
whatever it is.
You want an electric fan
that blows hot air?
I got ya!
Looking for a shower that
sprays out chunks of ice?
Piece of cake for me!
I'm like that DJ Bombay.
Got a mat that's good for ten.
Just not for layin',
only standin'.
I liked what you did there.
- You got that reference?
- Yeah, I knew that!
Who?
Whatever you want, I got you.
I can make it work!
You're a damn hot cat, Nyx!
Ah, it's my turn!
You really saved me
for last, huh?
What's mine?
Oh, my gosh. I'm so excited.
[CLEARS THROAT AWKWARDLY]
Looking good there, girl.
But they all got...
I like your eyeshadow,
it's a bit blue.
I'm done!
You're so unfair, I'm leaving.
But I really don't know
what you can do.
No, come on,
she's got something!
Daphne, uh...
Is it really that hard
to think of something?
What you offer...
Hmm...
- You want water?
- You are...
the Probability Queen!
'Cause she got problems?
- No!
- No, Nyx, probability.
- Probability.
- Probability is another thing.
Probability Queen, because...
Aren't you good
with computations?
- Right.
- And, you know, guys,
that's very, very important when
we start coming up with plans.
We need to know
the probability of success!
How cool!
A round of applause, please!
Please.
[APPLAUDING]
Nice save.
- Yes! Daphne!
- Thank you!
- Now, I've decided to stay!
- Yay!
Okay, good!
Now, thank you so much
for that wonderful presentation.
You know I did that
in a hurry, right?
What more if you got
more prep time, right?
But now, it's time.
It's game time.
For real, for real.
These are our targets.
We have Cole, Lester, Ant,
Migo, and Earl.
Let's include him anyway.
They are our targets,
and we have to get them
kicked out of school.
Yes. Because when
we kick them out of school,
we kick out their hopes,
their dreams,
their aspirations in life...
their reputation,
we'll crush all of those!
[DAPHNE] I like that.
Because what is
the most important goal
of a student in SOSH?
It's to graduate
with high honors.
And if we get them kicked out,
they lose all that!
All their hopes,
their dreams, everything!
They'll lose
their purpose in life!
- They're gonna be devastated!
- Yeah.
And let's not forget
Principal McKenna...
because she's complicit.
[DAPHNE] Ah, you're right.
And the board of directors, too.
Now, the floor is all yours.
It's now open
for comments, suggestions,
violent reactions, take it away!
This is a bad idea.
No!
If Cole finds out
about everything we're doing,
he'll tell the guys.
He'll tell our Dad!
I'm gonna get
in trouble with Dad.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
He'll throw me out of the house,
I won't be able to graduate
and then you'll just see me
on the streets of BGC,
begging for food!
[NYX] That's so fab, really.
- BGC?
- BGC...
- You don't want Poblacion?
- She'll do busking?
Hey, you're so negatron.
Well, what does
the "Probability Queen"
have to say about
the probability of success?
[PENSIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
[APRIL] My God, are you okay?
That's normal, guys.
- [ISOBEL] Girl?
- [CHUCKLES]
High.
I'll say
our success rate is 97%.
See how good I am,
I computed that.
[ISOBEL] Why don't we just
put them in a classroom
and bomb them!
Like what you said earlier.
Tick-tick...
Bomb.
Plus, I've been experimenting
on bombs and explosives.
In my kitchen.
Do you want me to show you?
J-joke... you're joking, right?
You're joking, right?
Girl, I don't want
the tech-tech to go boom.
I'm always joking.
[SIGHS]
She's a joker.
But she's got a point.
Let's just take them out, yeah?
I know someone in our community
who can take them out,
they can do it.
[MARLA] Okay, girls. Girls?
Let's establish
some ground rules, yeah?
Rule number one,
we will not murder anyone.
We will not hurt anyone.
Rule number two,
we will not hire anyone
to hurt anyone.
- Okay?
- But where is the fun in that?
Kidding!
Okay, who in that long list
are we going to kill
ruin first?
Let's get Migo first.
I'm sure he's the one
who leaked my pictures.
And he's resposible
for protecting them online.
Let's get him first!
Look at that stupid face,
it's annoying.
Stupid. He does look stupid.
Well, for me,
I'm thinking that,
we take Cole out first.
He's the leader after all.
And as John C. Maxwell said,
"Leadership is influence."
When the leader falls,
the minions follow.
Wait, wait,
Lester isn't a minion,
'cause he's the most dangerous
of them all.
And if you think about it,
he's also the hottest.
What I mean is,
they'll be weak without Lester.
Look who's getting weak.
Anyways...
why don't we just put them
in a classroom
and then give them
stimulant drugs
and then make them kill
one another
because we can't kill them,
but they can kill one another.
I want to see blood.
For once in my life...
Isobel is right.
What?
We can kill them?
- I was just joking...
- [MARLA] No, of course not.
I didn't mean "kill them".
What I meant was...
why target them one by one
when we can target them
all together?
- Right?
- [NYX] You got it!
I have an idea.
- [SNIFFS]
- [BELL DINGS]
- [GASPS]- The light?
How did you--
[DAPHNE] These spirits,
they're following--
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
["DON'T ASK ME WHY"
BY DNA PLAYING]
BY DNA CONTINUES]
["DON'T ASK ME WHY"
[MARLA] The Four Laws
of Thermodynamics.
Zeroth Law states...
if two systems are each
in thermal equilibrium
with a third system,
then they're
in thermal equilibrium
with each other.
If you think about this
in terms of justice,
we are destined
to reach an equilibrium
where every moral debt
is eventually leveled
and all accounts are settled.
What I meant to say is...
It's payback time!
["DON'T ASK ME WHY"
BY DNA CONTINUES]
- [MUSIC TENSES]
- So, look here.
I made this ESP32-CAM module
which combines microcontroller,
Wi-Fi, and camera,
all in one unit.
This microcontroller also known
as the "brain" of the robot.
It's this!
And here, here, here, here!
We're so going boom boom pow!
[MARLA] The First Law
of Thermodynamics.
Everyone follow me. Hurry!
- Energy cannot be created
- Let's go! Let's go!
- or destroyed.
- Go!
- Only transferred or changed
- Here, faster!
from one form to another.
Okay, there, there, there.
[NYX] Five,
for the five little boys.
They're all going boom boom pow.
We've got two micro servos.
One so we can tilt--
It's time to get back
at the boys
- with the same amount of energy
- we can pan,
- and transfer some of the pain
- round direction
- to them.
- if ever we want it to face up,
or look down,
to the left, the right,
or any other direction!
Okay, go, let's all be careful.
[THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING]
This is brilliant!
Perfect!
Okay.
[MARLA] The Third Law states
that the entropy of a system
approaches
a constant minimum value
as its temperature
approaches absolute zero,
where all motion ceases.
This simply means that
there's no turning back.
Once we get started,
there's no end
until we achieve victory.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Marla.
Hmm?
[WARREN] How are you?
Are you okay?
- [TEACHER] Ms. Calaquian, move!
- [MARLA] I'm good.
Never been better.
Really?
What do you think?
[SNIFFS]
Sorry, that was a dumb question.
- Lester, my guy!
- Yes, sir!
I've never been this popular,
but for the wrong reasons.
April?
April!
You know, if only...
I can disappear,
even for just a week
just be invisible,
just so I can straighten
my life out.
Eleanor Roosevelt once said,
"A woman is like a tea bag,
you'll never know
how strong she is
until she's in hot water."
Well, I'm in hot water
and everyone knows the tea.
Hey, hey! [CHUCKLES]
Yeah!
Marla,
I didn't look at the photos.
Why?
You didn't like them?
- I didn't do it for you.
- Huh? [LAUGHS]
No, um...
I'm just kidding. [LAUGHING]
[SIGHS]
Okay...
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
But...
I'm pretty sure that...
you look real good in them.
[LAUGHS LIGHTLY]
I'm pretty sure
you look gorgeous
even when you're naked.
Oh, I mean,
you always look great...
in every day that God made,
Sorry.
I don't know what I'm saying.
But, seriously...
why?
Why didn't you look?
I just can't.
Why not?
Everyone else has seen it.
Join the club.
Have you seen the memes?
The weird, creepy AI videos?
And I know it's going to be
on the internet forever.
It can't be deleted completely.
So if you change your mind,
you can always take a look.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
Marla, I really can't look
at it...
because it's you.
You're Marla.
I respect you.
And I'm supposed
to be impressed?
I... I don't know. [LAUGHS]
Maybe not. I mean...
what I did wasn't really
that impressive.
Mm.
[WARREN] Are you still
with Cole?
Going strong?
- We broke up.
- I'm sorry.
Was it him?
Was he the reason
behind all of your suffering?
He said...
it wasn't him.
I wanna believe in that.
But you're not sure?
I don't know.
I don't know anything
at this point.
I don't think Cole
could do that to you.
'Cause you're his girlfriend.
I mean, ex-girlfriend.
But if you're my girlfriend...
If I'm your girlfriend, then?
If-- if you're my girlfriend...
- Uh...
- [MARLA GIGGLES]
You'll take care of me?
You won't hurt me?
You won't neglect me,
you'll be gentle with me?
Hmm?
Come on. I've heard
all that before.
Not from me though.
Hmm?
I want you to hear
from me directly...
that I'll take care of you.
I'll show you
that I love you everyday.
That's if you're
my girlfriend...
[SOFT ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[LAUGHS] But I'm not.
I know. [LAUGHING]
- I did say "if only."
- Mm-hmm. [GIGGLING]
- [WHISTLE BLOWS]
- Time's up! Hit the showers!
- [SIGHS]
- Oh!
Hey.
Thank you for not looking.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, I'll go ahead, yeah?
[WARREN] Ah...
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [WATER POURING]
- [SNEEZES]
[GROANING]
[GATE CLANKS]
[WHISPERING] Come on.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Ready?
It's showtime!
[PHONES BEEPING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WHISPERING] Nyx!
It's too foggy.
I can't see anything!
We didn't anticipate
the steam!
How are we gonna record?
[HUFFING]
I've computed
our probability of success.
Fifty percent!
- No! Abort mission!
- Shh!
This project
was dead on arrival.
The boys
will definitely find out
and get back at us.
What if they kidnap me
and tie me up
in some warehouse in Bulacan!
- So negative!
- I shouldn't have joined!
A warehouse in Bulacan? Really?
All that planning and nobody
thought about condensation.
We're such geniuses.
Calm down. It's getting
my armpits sweaty.
My deodorant has no extra hold.
Hold up.
[RUSTLING]
[CLACKS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[CLACKS, WHIRRS]
Let's drive?
Go, let's go!
Go!
[TIMER BEEPING SFX]
[TOY CAR WHEELS WHIRRING]
Ka-chow!
[NYX] Hmph!
Nyx! I could kiss you right now,
you're a genius!
Aren't we all geniuses?
You think
that's the exciting part?
- What?
- Just you wait.
We're just getting
to the exciting part.
What?!
- Exciting part?
- What'd she say?
You better not move
or else I'll kill you.
Wh-- why do you have
a gas mask?!
Hey, Isobel!
[GRUNTS NERVOUSLY]
[WATER POURING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
[JAR RATTLING]
[JAR OPENS]
[OBJECTS THUDDING LIGHTLY]
[SCRUNCHING]
[THUDDING]
[SQUEAKING]
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[COUGHING]
Isobel, what's wrong with you?!
- Girl, what did you do?!
- Chill.
- Hold on to your panties.
- I told you, "No killing!"
No, no. You can't!
The boys are gonna die!
We'll get charged
with first degree murder!
Or homicide!
Yellow shirts don't suit me!
- Hey, we can't go to--
- Maybe they have orange ones?
- Orange? Orange?
- Orange!
- Orange doesn't suit me either!
- Shh!
Don't you trust me enough?
- You crazy, why did you--
- Shut up.
Things are about to get hot.
[BOYS COUGHING INTENSELY]
[LAUGHING HYSTERICALLY]
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[APRIL] Are we recording this?
Because this is gonna be
such a scandal!
I know, right?
[MOANING]
Nyx, hey!
- [GASPS]
- Oh, my gosh!
Ew, you're so disgusting!
[MOANING]
[TENSE ELECTRONIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE ELECTRONIC MUSIC
CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
[FOOTSTEPS RETREATING]
- Oh!
- [GIRLS GRUNTING]
Isobel?!
It's Warren!
Then do something!
- He might get into--
- The fun?
- Hey!
- No!
I think he can join in the fun!
Nyx!
Be strong!
Now what?
You do it!
Why me?
- Can I do it?
- No!
- Have fun.
- Go.
Shh!
Ah, slay!
Hi! Warren!
Hello!
What are you doing here?
Welcome!
Why are you
in the boys' locker room?
Uh...
I'm guarding the door.
They're in trouble over there.
Trouble?
- What's happening?
- Oh, no, no! Uh...
It's not trouble, it's...
it's happiness.
Marla, what's going on?
Nothing! Nothing's going on!
- Besides...
- Let me through.
Besides you're not welcome,
because...
it's exclusive to them.
Since when did
the boys' locker room
become exclusive to them?
Today! As of today.
- Marla, let me through.
- No, uh... No, no, no!
- If there's trouble I need to--
- No, no, no, no!
There's no trouble,
it's just a joke!
I was mistaken.
We all make mistakes.
Whoa! Whoa! Hold up!
[DAPHNE] Hey, Isobel! Isobel!
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
- [MARLA GASPS]
- [TWINKLING SFX]
[SMOOCHES]
Go away!
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Now!
- [PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [BREATHES DEEPLY]
Y-You can't just go around
kissing other people
without their consent!
He seemed to have enjoyed it.
That's not the point.
Marla,
my nude photos were released
without my consent,
so I don't care at this point!
But that wasn't part
of the plan, right?
I'm guessing you're a Virgo?
Things always need to go
according to plan.
Come on, you have to learn
how to be flexible.
If I hadn't kissed Warren,
it would've ruined
all our plans.
And I'm guessing
you're a Scorpio?
Doing impulsive things
without thinking
- about the consequences!
- I'm a Capricorn. You?
I'm a Libra.
I don't know
why you're reacting this way.
Shh!
If you wanted to kiss Warren,
you should've just gone for it.
[SCOFFS] What? No!
I didn't want to kiss Warren!
You look so jealous right now.
[SCOFFS]
Is this about Warren
or someone else?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Let's just cut to the chase.
Quit it. Stop!
Shh...
The past is the poison
to our plans right now.
Don't go there.
Shh!
Keep your voice down!
Girls, they'll hear us.
Yeah. We've already nailed the
landing. We're successful.
No need to fight.
See?
My calculations were right.
Do you believe
in my superpowers now?
- Girl! Girl!
- No!
Girl, next time
there's a kissing scene,
tell me beforehand,
so I can take over.
- I'll volunteer, okay?
- Come on! Keep it together!
- Nyx!
- [SNAPS FINGERS]
- Stop.
- Let's go!
There wouldn't be any argument
if I got to kiss him, right?
[TRIUMPHANT SYNTH MUSIC PLAYING]
[TRIUMPHANT SYNTH MUSIC
CONTINUES]
It's showtime!
[BOYS MOANING ON VIDEO]
[STUDENT ON VIDEO]
Fuck.
- [MOANING CONTINUES]
- [INTENSE TECHNO MUSIC PLAYING]
Fuck.
Ah... shit.
[MOANING CONTINUES,
BREATHING HEAVILY]
[INTENSE TECHNO MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MOANING CONTINUES]
[MUMBLING, BREATHING HEAVILY]
- Oh my...
- Shit...
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[BOYS MOANING ON VIDEO]
Shit.
Fuck.
- Fuck.
- Ah!
[MOANING,
BREATHING HEAVILY CONTINUES]
[INTENSE TECHNO MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [MOANING LOUDLY]
- [HISSING]
[INTENSE TECHNO MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
[SLOW CLAPPING]
[CLAPPING, CHEERING]
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC BECOMES OMINOUS]
Is it just me,
or are they being praised?
Girl, they're being praised!
That was rhetorical, Nyx!
I-I thought the odds of success
were high, Daphne?
That's why
it's called probability.
There's still a chance
it could go completely wrong.
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
- [CHEERING CONTINUES]
- [OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [STUDENT 1 LAUGHS]
- [STUDENT 2 SQUEALS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BREATHING HEAVILY
IN FRUSTRATION]
- [CHEERING, CLAPPING]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Goddammit!
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]